ROMA KHAYDAROV

AREA SALES EXECUTIVE









I am very intuitive and can use this ability to understand the best way to approach a possible sale. I am great with colleagues and customers alike and very easy going. I enjoy advising people on products and services. Expert Sales executive with goods and parfums expertise and 2 years of experience in Dubai Dutyfree ambassador shop . Proven ability to effectively lead personnel in various combat and non-combat situations. Strong problem-solving abilities, committed to achieving goals with friendly and strong team .

EDUCATION

HIGHER NATIONAL DIPLOMA

Turkish Economical college / Istanbul , Türkey 2015

DRIVING LICENSE

Driving license category

Galadari driving school License

PERSONAL DETAILS

Date of birth

16 July 1995

Visa status

Residence Visa

Marital status

Single

LANGUAGES

English

Turkish

Russian

WORK EXPERIENCE

AREA SALES EXECUTIVE

Ambassador External Dubai Dutyfree / Nov 2018 - Present / Dubai , United Arab Emirates

- Assessed changing markets, customer conditions, and competitor data and initiated update of account plans accordingly.
- Identified and then implemented a more efficient method of sending products to customers, which received all-round positive feedback.
- Assisted clients in deploying effective advertising to increase their business opportunities.
- Producted high-quality advertising according to requirement in collaboration with graphic designers.
- Meeting daily , weekl and monthly targets.
- Listened to customer complaints and took measures to eliminate issues or made adjustments to operations resulting in an increase in customer satisfaction.
- Made adjustments to sales procedures by tracking customer behavior, market trends, and current market share to realign company goals.

CASHIER/SALES ASSOCIATE

Aldo shop / Oct 2016 - Oct 2018 / Ras Al Khaima , United Arab Emirates

- Increased customer sales by providing knowledge and demonstrating features of various merchandise.
- Provided assistance to customers to find appropriate products, answered questions and provided solutions for issues.
- $\bullet~$ Found items from store and other locations for customers to purchase.
- Received training to step into roles in other departments to provide assistance when needed.
- Assisted in controlling store shoplifting, provided security with description of suspected thieves.

SALES ASSISTANT

Romano Botta / Dec 2015 - Aug 2016 / Istanbul, Turkey

- Work with customers with the most cheerful and pleasant disposition
- Give answers to customers' questions or concerns related to the product they are charged to sell and demonstrate good knowledge of the product
- Communicate and assist customers in any way possible and as the customers may require
- Deal with customer's complaints professionally and with restraint
- Close as many deals and transactions as possible
- Process or help process payments made by the customer whether by in cash or credit card
- \bullet Bag products for the customers (if there's no other assigned to that)